amyshealthybaking.com 2019-03-31

# Disclosure and Privacy Policy | Amy's Healthy Baking

**Disclosure Policy**  
This policy is valid from June 2014.

_Amy’s Healthy Baking_ is a personal blog written and edited by Amy. For any inquiries, please contact Amy by filling out [this form](https://amyshealthybaking.com/about/contact/ "Contact").

This blog accepts various forms of paid advertising, sponsorship, or other forms of compensation. This blog is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for Amy to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

This blog is not paid to express an explicit opinion on particular websites, products, and/or services; all opinions are always Amy’s own. Any endorsements made regarding a particular website, product, and/or service are made because Amy genuinely believes in and enjoys the object of the endorsement.

**Privacy Policy**   
We may collect the following information: contact information including email address, demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests, other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers. 

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: we may use the information to improve our products and service, and we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes; and if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.
